<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Haryana ka Master</string>
    <string name="base_url"></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="share_message">
        Check out this fabulous educational app! 📚 Use my referral code %1$s to get up to 50% off. Download now: %2$s
    </string>
    <string name="about_us">Developed by 5g Infotech</string>
    <string name="tc">Terms and condition</string>
    <string name="pp"><![CDATA[1. Privacy Policy\nAt Haryana Math Master, accessible via http://lifelearningeducation.in/, we are committed to safeguarding your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By using our website, you agree to the practices described below.\n\nInformation We Collect\nWe may collect the following types of personal information:\n\nName, email address, phone number, and address\nPayment details (processed securely through third-party gateways)\nUsage data and cookies for improving user experience\nHow We Use Your Information\nWe use your personal information to:\n\nProvide and deliver our educational services\nRespond to your inquiries and support requests\nProcess payments and issue invoices\nImprove website functionality and analyze usage trends\nSharing Your Information\nWe do not share your personal information with third parties, except as required by law or to provide our services (e.g., payment processors).\n\nData Security\nWe use appropriate technical measures to protect your personal data from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.\n\nYour Rights\nYou have the right to access, update, or delete your personal information. For any queries, contact us at support@lifelearningeducation.in.\n\n\n\n2. Return & Refund Policy\nWe have a 30-day return policy, which means you have 30 days after receiving your item to request a return.\n\nTo be eligible for a return, your item must be in the same condition that you received it, unworn or unused, with tags, and in its original packaging. You’ll also need the receipt or proof of purchase.\n\nTo start a return, you can contact us at Support@lifelearningeducation.in.\n\nIf your return is accepted, we’ll send you a return shipping label, as well as instructions on how and where to send your package. Items sent back to us without first requesting a return will not be accepted.\n\nYou can always contact us for any return-related questions at Support@lifelearningeducation.in.\n\nEuropean Union 14-Day Cooling Off Period\nNotwithstanding the above, if the merchandise is being shipped into the European Union, you have the right to cancel or return your order within 14 days, for any reason and without a justification. As mentioned above, your item must be in the same condition that you received it, unworn or unused, with tags, and in its original packaging. You’ll also need the receipt or proof of purchase.\n\nRefunds\nWe will notify you once we’ve received and inspected your return and let you know if the refund was approved or not. If approved, you’ll be automatically refunded on your original payment method within 10 business days. Please remember it can take some time for your bank or credit card company to process and post the refund too.\nIf more than 15 business days have passed since we’ve approved your return, please contact us at Support@lifelearningeducation.in.\n\n\n3. Shipping Policy\n\nProcessing Time: Orders are typically processed and shipped within the same business day for prepaid orders and cash-on-delivery orders. Processing times may vary depending on product availability and order volume.\n\nShipping Methods: We offer various shipping options, including standard shipping, expedited shipping, and express shipping. The available shipping methods and associated costs will be displayed during the checkout process.\n\nShipping Restrictions: Some products may be subject to shipping restrictions based on their size, weight, or destination. We do not ship to P.O. boxes or APO/FPO addresses.\n\nShipping Costs: Shipping costs are calculated based on the weight of the package, the shipping method selected, and the delivery destination. The shipping cost will be displayed during the checkout process before you complete your purchase.\n\nDelivery Time: Delivery times vary depending on the shipping method selected and the destination. Estimated delivery times will be provided during the checkout process and are based on standard shipping times provided by the carrier.\n\nOrder Tracking: Once your order has been shipped, you will receive a shipping confirmation email containing tracking information. You can use this tracking information to monitor the status of your delivery.\n\nInternational Shipping: We offer international shipping to select countries. International orders may be subject to customs clearance procedures, which can cause delays beyond our original delivery estimates. Customers are responsible for any customs duties or taxes imposed by their country\'s customs authorities.\n\nLost or Damaged Shipments: In the event that your shipment is lost or damaged during transit, please contact our customer support team immediately. We will work with the carrier to resolve the issue and ensure that you receive your order as quickly as possible.\n\nShipping Policy Updates: Haryana Math Master reserves the right to update or modify this Shipping Policy at any time without prior notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the website.\n\nContact Us: For inquiries, concerns, or assistance regarding our Shipping Policy, please contact our customer support team at Support@lifelearningeducation.in.\n\nBy placing an order on the Haryana Math Master platform, you agree to comply with our Shipping Policy.\n\nLet me know if you\'d like to make further adjustments or add specific details.\n\n\n\n\n4. Terms and Conditions\n\nWelcome to Haryana Math Master! These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of our website and services, located at http://lifelearningeducation.in/.\n\nBy accessing this website, we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Haryana Math Master if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.\n\n1. Definitions\n\"Company\" refers to Haryana Math Master.\n\"You\" refers to the user or visitor of this website.\n\"Services\" refers to all products, content, and features provided by the Company through this website.\n2. Use of the Website\nYou must be at least 18 years old or have parental/guardian consent to use our services.\nBy using this website, you agree to provide accurate and complete information when required.\nAny misuse of the website for illegal activities is strictly prohibited.\n3. Intellectual Property Rights\nUnless otherwise stated, Haryana Math Master owns the intellectual property rights for all material on this website. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this material for personal use, subject to the restrictions set in these terms and conditions.\n\nYou must not:\n\nRepublish, sell, rent, or sub-license material from this website.\nReproduce, duplicate, or copy material from this website.\nRedistribute content from Haryana Math Master without prior written permission.\n4. Services and Payments\nAll services offered are subject to availability and may be withdrawn or modified without prior notice.\nPayments must be made in full before access to certain courses, products, or features is granted.\nPricing details for services and products are clearly mentioned on the website and are subject to change.\n5. User Accounts\nTo access some parts of the website, you may need to create an account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account details.\nThe Company reserves the right to terminate accounts or refuse service at our sole discretion if these terms are violated.\n6. Cancellation and Termination\nHaryana Math Master reserves the right to cancel or terminate services or accounts for violations of these terms or other unlawful behavior.\nIn case of termination, users may lose access to any course, subscription, or service without a refund.\n7. Limitation of Liability\nHaryana Math Master will not be held responsible for any damages resulting from the use or inability to use our services. This includes direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages.\n\n8. External Links\nOur website may contain links to external websites for reference purposes. Haryana Math Master does not control or endorse the content on these external websites and is not responsible for any damages caused by their use.\n\n9. Privacy Policy\nYour use of the website is also governed by our Privacy Policy, which can be found on the website.\n\n10. Changes to Terms and Conditions\nHaryana Math Master reserves the right to update or modify these terms at any time without prior notice. By continuing to use the website after such changes, you agree to the updated terms.\n\n11. Governing Law\nThese terms and conditions are governed by the laws of India. Any disputes arising in relation to these terms shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Haryana, India.\n\n12. Contact Us\nIf you have any questions about these terms and conditions, please contact us at:\nEmail: Support@lifelearningeducation.in\n\n\n\n5. Disclaimer\n\nThe information provided on the website http://lifelearningeducation.in/ is for general informational purposes only. Haryana Math Master makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability, or availability of the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.\n\n1. Educational Content\nHaryana Math Master provides educational resources and services to help users enhance their knowledge and skills. However, the content on this website should not be taken as professional or expert advice. Users are encouraged to use the materials for learning purposes only and to consult with experts for professional advice if needed.\n\n2. No Guarantee of Results\nWhile we strive to provide high-quality learning materials, Haryana Math Master does not guarantee that users will achieve specific results or outcomes through the use of our services, courses, or products.\n\n3. External Links Disclaimer\nOur website may contain links to external websites or third-party content. Haryana Math Master does not control or endorse the information, services, or products available on these external websites. We are not responsible for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party websites.\n\n4. Limitation of Liability\nIn no event will Haryana Math Master be liable for any loss or damage, including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from the use of this website or its services.\n\n5. Technical Issues\nWhile we make every effort to keep the website running smoothly, Haryana Math Master takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.\n\n6. Updates to the Disclaimer\nHaryana Math Master reserves the right to update or modify this Disclaimer at any time without prior notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the website.\n\n7. Contact Us\nIf you have any questions about this Disclaimer, please contact us at:\nEmail: Support@lifelearningeducation.in\n]]></string>
</resources>